<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recents Article on Portio</title>
    <link>www.wemobilize.dk/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recents Article on Portio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="www.wemobilize.dk/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Setting up startup infrastructure</title>
      <link>www.wemobilize.dk/blog/it_infrastructure_when_setting_up_company/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.wemobilize.dk/blog/it_infrastructure_when_setting_up_company/</guid>
      <description>I am currently starting my next phase of professional life involving being a CTO as a Service for two startups, initially. One thing than any company needs is basic IT infrastructure. Based on my experiences the last 7 years in LetsBuild and talking to various other people in my network, the following systems form the cornerstone of the companies
 Google Workspace - Email, Calendar  When setting up mail, it&amp;rsquo;s important to setup SPF, DKIM and DMARC to avoid that the mail lands in receiver&amp;rsquo;s spam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up my own blog</title>
      <link>www.wemobilize.dk/blog/setting_up_a_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.wemobilize.dk/blog/setting_up_a_blog/</guid>
      <description>I like statically generated web-sites. Using them skips a lot of heavy infrastructure and potential trouble securing that. So unless you need a large largely non technical marketing department running your website, and you are a little tech savy (which I should be in my job, good to keep in touch with the base). So I tried a few things, first Jekyll which supposedly is the major one out there, but it runs on ruby and ruby is a complex beast to install and maintain in different versions (probably not first time, but when you come back later, you can spend a lot of time just getting it right; a bit similar with Python.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
